[{"answer": "Christ, I wish you'd stayed home tonight", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And you know what you are?  You're disgusting", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " For the next few hours, you're to warn me of my friend's every approach and you may have to screen me from public view in the likely event I that I throw up. It's that bad", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Nothing good about it, I assure you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Sounds like a real goodie", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Don't insult me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes.   What's stopping us", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You won't be getting any kind of job, because I will", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Ah, my friend. Good to see your shining face.  What's the news", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Right.   And I'm moving to that place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "There's something I should have mentioned earlier... I'm leaving the firm. In the fall", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, it's not another outfit", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, hi my friend. Working late", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I heard you were getting promoted", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Big shot. I guess your Dad would have been real proud, huh", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " So...", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm going to take my doll carriage and my bear and my three Easter rabbits and my giraffe and all my dolls and my doll house", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No! I don't want to give it to my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You've been inside all day", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, I don't feel like explaining everything fifteen times to somebody who's too bored and silly to listen", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "...And supposing you're right. You make all this money and we have this interesting life here. Won't you still be wasting your life toiling away at a job you find ridiculous? Just like your father", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Your business", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How can it be for me if the thought makes my stomach turn over", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "We can't have the baby in that place", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, my friend. I couldn't even understand half the things he told me. He said the fetus was out before they got her here. He said they had to operate to take out the whatdycallit, the placenta and now she's still bleeding. He said she'd lost a lot of blood before the ambulance came, and now they're trying to stop it, and he said a whole lot of things I didn't get, about capillaries, and he said she's unconscious. my friend", "docId": "Revolutionary-Road.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What the hell do I want to sit down for", "qsentId": 26}]